gograph.com 2018-09-03

# Privacy Policy - GoGraph

Privacy Policy

There is certain information that we collect about you so that we may do business with you and improve the service we provide to you on our website. This Privacy Policy describes how we collect and retain personal information, why we collect it, how we use it, and how you are able to access, update, delete, and export your information. “Personal Information” includes any information that relates to, identifies, or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains. We may make changes to this policy on occasion, and the most current version of this policy will be posted at www.gograph.com/privacy/. 

By using this Site, you understand and agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. This Site is operated in the United States and may be accessed abroad. For data protection purposes, Company is the controller and, unless otherwise noted, is also the processor of data. Personal Information collected may be retained, and may be stored, processed, accessed, and used in jurisdictions whose privacy laws may be different and less protective than those of your home jurisdiction. 

Which information we collect and why we collect it:

  * When you register with us, we collect your name, company name, phone number, address, email address, username, and password (“Information”). You may choose not to provide this information by not registering with us, however, certain products and services on the Site are only available to you upon registration. Once you register with us, you will be able to create lightboxes and view unwatermarked comps. Lightboxes allow you to collect images you like and organize them by client, category, or any other way you wish. You consent to the use of your Information as designated in this policy when you register with us. It is your responsibility to keep your password confidential. 
  * When you make a purchase with us, we collect your Information and your credit card information including number, expiration date, card type, and billing address or your credit card, which we need in order to process your orders, complete payment, and for license transaction history record keeping purposes. Your credit card information is stored in a secure location and is transmitted to us through a secure location. We only allow access to your credit card information to authorized personnel. 
  * In order to determine what our customers are interested in, we may collect certain technical and routing information about your computer or mobile app and your use of our website, including IP (Internet Protocol) addresses, cookie identifiers, web beacons, log files, browser type, operating system, CPU speed, device data, website activity, and information from online advertisers or third parties that help us determine which products to show you (“Data”) so we may improve our service, and for targeted advertising. 
  * Your orders, details about your purchases, your favorites, searches, downloads, logins, data and content submissions, support requests, and other miscellaneous information are kept by us, which is only accessible to authorized personnel. 
  * We may include social media features on our website, such as Facebook, Pinterest, Twitter, LinkedIn, and Google/Google Plus widgets or buttons, and these features may collect your IP address and the pages you are visiting on our site, and set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. If you sign on to our site using social media, those services may provide you the option to share certain personal information with us. 

Emails from GoGraph:

  * When you register with us, we collect your email address so we are able to notify you by email of special offers and discounts, some of which are only available to you via such emails. 
  * If you care to unsubscribe from our email list at any time, you may send an email to [unsubscribe@gograph.com](mailto:unsubscribe@gograph.com) from the email address you care to have removed, and you should not receive emails of that type from us in the future. 
  * Upon creating your account, you may receive a series of welcome emails, confirming your account creation and informing you about how to use the site. To prevent receiving these messages, do not create an account, or otherwise cancel your account. 
  * You may receive transactional emails as a result of requests you initiate (e.g. forgotten password, emailed purchased images) and notifications as a result of actions you have taken (payment requests, support ticket notifications, purchase receipts, notification of upcoming or past subscription renewals, subscription expirations, credit replenishments, low credit balances, etc.). To prevent receiving these messages, you must either not use your account, or cancel your account. 

Accessing, updating, deleting, or exporting your Information:

  * You may update your Contact Information at any time by going to My Account. 
  * To receive information we collect about you, or to request that we correct, revise, remove, or delete your data, provide your email address and submit a request. We will supply or remove the associated data within thirty (30) days of your request. 
  * To obtain information about whether we hold or process any of your Personal Information on behalf of a third party, please [contact us](mailto:privacy@gograph.com).
  * You have the right to revise your privacy preferences at any time and to do so, please [contact us](mailto:privacy@gograph.com). We will respond to your request within a reasonable period of time. 
  * We do not intend to solicit or collect Personal Information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are under 18, do not enter information on this site or engage our services. If you believe a child of yours under the age of 18 has entered Personal Information please [contact us](mailto:privacy@gograph.com) to have the data removed and terminate the child’s account. 

Information Sharing:

  * GoGraph may disclose the Information to companies in our corporate group; service providers such as retailers, online and offline advertisers, and companies who help market our products; carefully selected business partners; and others, such as non-profit organizations, and third parties. 
  * Third parties may use the Data to target advertising on other websites and may place cookies on users’ browsers for targeted advertising purposes as a result of visiting our website 
  * GoGraph may use your name and logo in disclosing that you are a customer.
  * We may disclose Personal Information if required by law (for example, to comply with a subpoena, warrant, court order, or legal process) or when necessary to protect our rights, avoid litigation, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, and/or respond to a government request. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that such disclosure should be made for reasons of national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance. 
  * To discontinue receiving targeted advertising, you may opt out on the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out website, located at [www.networkadvertising.org/choices/](https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/). 

Data Retention:

  * We will retain your Personal Information for as long as your account is active, your information is needed to provide you services, or as required to fulfill our legal and accounting requirements, resolve disputes, and comply with our agreements. If you wish to delete your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, please submit a request. We will respond to your request within a reasonable amount of time. 

Security of our Data:

  * You may submit your order to GoGraph over a secure connection and your credit card information is stored in a secure location, accessible only to authorized personnel. 
  * Although we take reasonable precautions to keep secure the information disclosed to us, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third party that received the information. 

© 2018 Publitek, Inc. dba GoGraph. All rights reserved. Revision date: May 25, 2018

#### Satisfaction Guarantee

Your satisfaction is important to us. If you are unsatisfied for any reason, we offer a 100%% money back guarantee for up to 30 days after your purchase.
